Welcome to discourse.
토론에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
So from our previous video we have created a new lane finder function.
그래서 이전 비디오에서 새로운 차선 찾기 기능을 만들었습니다.
So if I run my program from of a lean finder function we have created these two green lines and now
따라서 린 파인더 기능에서 내 프로그램을 실행하면 이 두 개의 녹색 선이 생성되었으며 이제
in the next step from these two lanes I will find a lean center.
이 두 차선의 다음 단계에서 나는 린 센터를 찾을 것입니다.
So let's find a lane center.
그럼 차선 중심을 찾아봅시다.
This is my lane center.
제 레인 센터입니다.
So the question is how I can find that distance for this lane center.
따라서 문제는 이 차선 중심에 대한 거리를 어떻게 찾을 수 있느냐는 것입니다.
I have the value of it.
나는 그것의 가치가 있습니다.
That means my left lane position.
내 왼쪽 차선 위치를 의미합니다.
I also have a value of B.
나는 또한 B의 값을 가지고 있습니다.
That means my right lane condition and I can simply find the lane center from E and B.
그것은 나의 오른쪽 차선 상태를 의미하며 E와 B에서 차선 중심을 간단히 찾을 수 있습니다.
So with the mathematics the lane center will be B minus eight divided by two plus E.
따라서 수학적으로 차선 중심은 B 빼기 8 나누기 2 더하기 E가 됩니다.
So let us implement scheme in the C++ here for this task.
따라서 여기에서 이 작업을 위해 C++에서 체계를 구현해 보겠습니다.
I will create a new function so let us create a new function.
새 함수를 만들 것이므로 새 함수를 만들어 보겠습니다.
The function name there say Lane Center
기능 이름은 Lane Center라고 합니다.
for a Bill Lane Center.
빌 레인 센터를 위해.
I have to create a new integer variable so let's see Lane center
새로운 정수 변수를 생성해야 하므로 Lane 중심을 보겠습니다.
and this land center will be a word rightly in position.
그리고 이 땅의 중심은 올바른 위치에 있는 단어가 될 것입니다.
This is a will right lane position minus left lane position
이것은 의지 오른쪽 차선 위치에서 왼쪽 차선 위치를 뺀 값입니다.
divided by two plus left lane position
2 더하기 왼쪽 차선 위치로 나눈 값
and a left round bracket here.
여기에 왼쪽 둥근 브래킷이 있습니다.
Next I have to create a new variable.
다음으로 새 변수를 만들어야 합니다.
So this will also be integer variable and the name of the variable will be frame center.
따라서 이것은 또한 정수 변수가 될 것이며 변수의 이름은 프레임 중심이 될 것입니다.
Now what will be our frame center.
이제 프레임 센터가 될 것입니다.
It's simply 200 because I will frame is 400 and a frame center is 200
프레임이 400이고 프레임 중심이 200이기 때문에 단순히 200입니다.
next.
I have to declared all these variables globally.
이 모든 변수를 전역적으로 선언해야 합니다.
Next day I will declare somewhere here.
다음날 나는 여기 어딘가에 선언 할 것입니다.
First is our frame center.
먼저 프레임 센터입니다.
And second one is of a lane center.
그리고 두 번째는 레인 센터입니다.
I will draw a line from this lane center on the image.
이미지의 이 차선 중심에서 선을 그립니다.
So our values align feature
따라서 우리의 가치는 기능을 정렬합니다.
all right.
So let's call this function in the y loop.
y 루프에서 이 함수를 호출해 보겠습니다.
I will call it here.
나는 그것을 여기에서 부를 것이다.
This is my lane center.
제 레인 센터입니다.
Let's build the program now run the program.
이제 프로그램을 빌드해 보겠습니다.
All right.
So this is our lead center.
이것이 우리의 리드 센터입니다.
I'm the same way.
나도 마찬가지야.
I will also display a frame center here.
여기에 프레임 센터도 표시합니다.
Now go to the same function just copy this
이제 동일한 기능으로 이동하여 이것을 복사하십시오.
this time.
이 시간.
This will be over a Freedom Center.
이것은 자유 센터를 넘을 것입니다.
This will be also framed center.
이것은 또한 프레임 중심이 될 것입니다.
And for the color I just want to use the blue color.
그리고 색상에는 파란색을 사용하고 싶습니다.
So BGR I will change the 0 to 255 and green channel.
그래서 BGR I는 0을 255로 변경하고 녹색 채널을 변경합니다.
I will make the intensity to zero.
강도를 0으로 만들겠습니다.
Let's build a program.
프로그램을 만들어 봅시다.
Let's run the program.
All right.
So this green line is of a line center and blue line is our frame center.
따라서 이 녹색 선은 선 중심이고 파란색 선은 프레임 중심입니다.
So next step is our calibration.
따라서 다음 단계는 보정입니다.
So in our calibration process what we will do we will try to overlap with this learning center two of
따라서 교정 프로세스에서 수행할 작업은 다음 중 두 가지 학습 센터와 중복되도록 시도할 것입니다.
our frame center.
우리의 프레임 센터.
So first of all let's try to place of a rowboat exactly at the center of the lane like I'm placing my
따라서 우선 내가 보트를 배치하는 것처럼 정확하게 차선 중앙에 노 젓는 보트를 배치해 보겠습니다.
rowboat exactly at the center.
정확히 중앙에 노 젓는 배.
Make sure the space from the both side of your room board should be seen in order to do proper calibration.
적절한 보정을 수행하기 위해 룸 보드의 양쪽에서 공간이 보여야 합니다.
Now let's run the program again.
이제 프로그램을 다시 실행해 보겠습니다.
So this time our robot is actually at the center.
그래서 이번에는 로봇이 실제로 중앙에 있습니다.
So for this case we cannot change a word leaning Center because Leon Center is derived from over lines
따라서 이 경우 Leon Center가 over line에서 파생되기 때문에 단어 leaning Center를 변경할 수 없습니다.
but we can change the frame center in order to merge with this Leon Center.
그러나 이 Leon Center와 병합하기 위해 프레임 중심을 변경할 수 있습니다.
So whatever we do I try to shift this frame center to the left hand side so that it can easily overlap
그래서 우리가 무엇을 하든 이 프레임 중심을 왼쪽으로 이동하여 쉽게 겹칠 수 있도록 합니다.
with our lead center.
우리의 리드 센터와 함께.
Now look for a wall frame center.
이제 벽 프레임 센터를 찾으십시오.
So we defined a frame center to 200.
그래서 우리는 프레임 중심을 200으로 정의했습니다.
So let us shifted to the left side.
그럼 왼쪽으로 이동해 보겠습니다.
Now I will define it as one 90 build program on game.
이제 게임에서 하나의 90 빌드 프로그램으로 정의하겠습니다.
Let's run this now.
Very small difference left just close the program shifted again.
아주 작은 차이는 프로그램을 닫으면 다시 쉬프트됩니다.
Let's say this time one idiot
이번에는 바보라고 하자
built up program and run it.
프로그램을 만들고 실행합니다.
All right so over Leon Center is properly or leapt by a well frame center.
좋아, 레온 센터는 적절하게 또는 웰 프레임 센터에 의해 뛰어 넘습니다.
So over calibration is done.
그래서 오버 캘리브레이션이 완료되었습니다.
We can close this
우리는 이것을 닫을 수 있습니다
at this point.
We're done with our image processing for of a self-driving car.
우리는 자율주행차에 대한 이미지 처리를 마쳤습니다.
So in the next step I will discuss how we can bring some useful data on our video frame.
따라서 다음 단계에서는 비디오 프레임에 유용한 데이터를 가져올 수 있는 방법에 대해 설명하겠습니다.